fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
It's a custom where balance is preserved
by fighting and removing life.
This is the friendship
of the Shinobi world.
This is a fight for life with the pride
of the village and
one's own dream on the line.
Heh, I'm convinced.
Anything is fine.
Just tell us the content
of that fight-for-life test.
Very well.
Now then, this is where I'd
like to explain the third exam.
But actually...
Please allow me, Gekko Hayate who was
given the task of judge, to speak first.
I leave it to you...
There's something... I'd like you all
to do...
before the third exam.
And that is a preliminary
to the third exam,
with participation in
the main battle on the line.
Preliminary?
What do you mean... preliminary?!
Sensei, I don't understand
the point of that preliminary.
Why aren't we doing the next exam
with the remaining test-takers?
This time around,
perhaps because the first and
second exams were easy,
there are a few too many
people left, you see.
In accordance with the rules
of the Chunin Exams,
a preliminary will be held in order to
reduce the number advancing.
N-No way!
As Hokage-sama said before,
many guests will be coming
to the third exam.
So we can't have long pointless matches
and our time is limited as well.
Therefore, those of you
not in top physical condition...
Hey, is he okay...?!
The teacher doesn't look well himself?!
Excuse me.
Those of you who wish to drop out,
please speak up now.
The preliminary will
begin immediately, so...
Immediately, you say...?!
But we finally made it through
the second exam.
This is a pain...
Huh? What about our meal?
Those who Pass
Cut Down to Half?!
It's a Fight Without Warning!!
Okay!
I'm going to do my best, no matter what!
I promised Kabuto-san, too...
And oh...
I forgot to mention this, but it will
be individual battles from now on.
It is your decision, so feel free
to raise your hands and drop out.
Who's going to quit?!
Sasuke-kun?!
The waves of pain are
coming faster...
Sasuke-kun... I knew it.
Sasuke-kun, you should quit
these preliminaries!
Huh?!
L-Look, you haven't been yourself
ever since you got worked
over by that Orochimaru guy!
That bruise hurts even now, right...?
Bruise...?
At this rate...!
I gave him a parting gift.
Sasuke-kun will definitely seek me...
in search of power.
You're the only one left.
Please...
Please, quit!
I'm... scared.
Sakura-chan...
I knew it.
What shall we do?
We should remove him
from the exams
and isolate him with
ANBU bodyguards on him.
We should recommend that
he retire immediately.
He's not the kind of type to
just obey like that...?!
After all, he's of the Uchiha clan.
What're you talking nonsense for?!
I'll make him stop, by force if needed!
The Curse Mark responds even
when one's just building up Chakra
and attempts to forcibly
extract his strength!
It's a prohibited Jutsu that eats
into the body of the one who uses a Jutsu!
It's a wonder that kid is even enduring it.
He should really already be dead!
Hokage-sama!
You're in no condition to
fight properly, Sasuke-kun...!
Shut up.
I understand!
Be quiet!
But you've been enduring the pain
this whole time, right?!
Please be quiet!
No matter what you say, Sasuke-kun...
I'm going to tell the teachers
about the bruise!
If I do that...
Well...
Oh...?!
What...?
Excuse me... I'll quit.
K-Kabuto-san...?
Let's see...
Yakushi Kabuto-kun of
the Leaf Village, correct?
Then, you may step back.
Okay.
Kabuto-san!
Why're you quitting?!
Tell me! Why?!
This guy...
I'm sorry, Naruto-kun...
But my body is worn out.
Actually before the first exam...
when I wrangled with
the guys from Sound Village,
I've had no hearing at all in my left ear.
To fight right away...
and to be told that my life would
also be on the line, I can't go on.
I've seen that face a few times.
As I recall, I think he dropped out
of the main battle before, as well.
What in the world is he thinking?
Anko.
Uh... yes.
Yakushi Kabuto.
According to the data,
he has failed six straight times.
What about his background?
From his time at the Academy,
he was a student who did
not really stand out,
and his grades were ordinary.
He finally passed the graduation
exam on his third try.
After that, as for the missions
he carried out,
two C-ranks and fourteen D-ranks.
It's not a battle record to
write home about.
However...
However...?
It's about before the Academy.
Hmm?
Do you remember the story...
about the one boy brought back
from the Kikyo Pass battle?
I remember.
As I recall, I heard an enemy boy survivor
at the battlefield
was taken back by a Jonin from
the medical unit.
So he's that boy...?
Don't take arbitrary actions.
Have you forgotten
Orochimaru-sama's orders?
I leave it to you guys.
You in particular, Yoroi-san.
There should be no problems
here with your ability.
This is where you can
show your strength.
Those of you who are irritated that
I'm ahead of you.
So you're Orochimaru-sama's favorite, huh?
Don't get all high and mighty, kid.
I understand, Senpai.
Oh.
Naruto-kun... Sasuke-kun...
I wanted to play with you guys
a little more.
But if I do more than this...
The old me might get stirred up.
I am a spy so far as it goes.
I cannot expose myself, here.
Also... if you are going to watch.
My role of information collecting
has served its purpose...
Orochimaru-sama.
I'll save the fun, for some other time...
Sasuke-kun...
And Naruto-kun...
You too.
Now then, there are no others
who will quit?
I must tell the teachers,
about Sasuke-kun's bruise!
Huh?!
Be quiet about this bruise.
Why're you acting tough like that?!
I don't want to watch you suffer
all the time anymore!
For me you are...!
This has nothing to do with you!
It's none of your business.
I said it once before...
I'm an avenger.
This is not just a mere exam to me.
The Chunin business has
nothing to do with me.
"Am I strong?"
All I want is the answer to that.
By fighting with those who are strong!
And...
I'm Gaara of the desert.
Hey, you there...
Identify yourself.
I declare.
You are absolutely no match for me.
If I have the opportunity to fight you
in the next exam,
we won't run or hide.
And they're... here!
I will not allow even you
to take my path away from me!
Sasuke-kun...
You!
What're you doing putting up
a front, you idiot?!
Here Sakura-chan is this worried about you...!
Naruto!
I want to fight you, too.
Huh?!
What Orochimaru said
is sitting on my mind.
I will let Sasuke do the test...
— and see how things go.
— Wha...?!
H-Hokage-sama...!
However, if the Curse Mark opens
and the power gets even a little bit
out of control,
get in there and stop it.
All right.
But...!
I understand.
Now then, we will begin the preliminaries.
The preliminaries to come
will be one-on-one individual battles.
In other words,
actual battle format.
There are now exactly twenty people,
so we will conduct ten battles.
The winners will be able to
advance to the third exam.
There are no rules at all.
You will fight until someone dies,
collapses... or admits defeat.
And... please admit defeat right away
if you don't want to die.
However, in case I judge
that a match is over...
err... I don't want to needlessly increase
dead bodies,
so I will intervene and stop the match
or something to that effect.
What holds the key to your destinies is...
Open it.
This.
The names of two foes will be
randomly selected and
displayed on this electronic signboard.
Now then, let's get right down to it
and announce the two names
for the first battle.
dSSKmuWqrUKEYa
TMtQtRcnWMYQdm
TJhPwprkGXgHMu
uffCerGdbqbpOB
oGRnVerzlwHjZB
cuqwGwPAgUjWSB
ceuzAvmeHmScoa
pNpcujmczodNQk
hwVqQPNgswkMEN
tJVpkpotHqTwBZ
yDCAyuVjJjhnTx
UUeBEVUdiSsgxr
oJLYQeEDtMWKSW
vUiHcBNbALNzif
SoeppBumDFBgUc
ecRYgpKFdHcyAT
jcFAaszRBQAYCf
OblHSDLFSwICYV
hLWoiKIrHyFNLO
kfpIyDwkVPBKBP
RZTqrnPgVSTvwb
SqglAFbeazecOp
fdOsctHbtjmWjK
uTfPrzMNXeLtLU
jYnkeNtguioPgu
xQSZiBXdYUvwKt
izvdmChaFKnsQc
FHafodExUhhpDB
rxyjjvJkQmpZBF
GPDuUyebuZibYF
xQrOJFhEvqjCkL
YppZGHoiiVhiMd
xFzdzcZhgxkAcz
SzRKNzCQQCblyG
fQWAsFRhVvScas
LUPNSEQIsHVYCG
OxRSUvAPLBMvcs
PPJlwuXYfGRgDP
fOOsXrDCwnJWHx
IcenggcrDMWyOw
bomSxDktKlOJwB
yxveqpgmItmuUO
ykUYzyjGHXhoaI
zetoWfAtBRdCAP
LVQoaPnTeQfsxY
JweLgXYHEVXMrY
ENawSwcpcAfrAE
SbCTjifXBeJCiS
WBVCvGmBUKTwvg
dNZTxBfwRojvXr
xBsQjjPcoHuBGO
BBOfvpTrajTjlE
QvQCnXnBqpfHWe
ujTzfTsrRuybxV
ZOYuwstupgjlFC
fGfDuqHvwunnDA
BpDurzAHFZhEeI
IWTCxIBBLsxeCi
wBlGmVaAaXRlgn
lHLIkPzNczEkrM
MHeRvURnSquXir
YdezoGHYQNdmpJ
KYtBUHwsEsxumt
robDTCAyvTaZBQ
dbMHxqGydldLdv
PAYaeUhkTPpUXi
VqCpxPJQELLuzF
jbOEUJOzdFimfW
itCNOSuMylZHbi
IqnpLMcvZhlBvK
pHXbzUpCQrpdDT
fMWmJLxivmShTm
VtwdGhAsUCpeSG
uMQSQyhIPIMfsn
PaflGPvobtMsYL
wDASeFrUJeRPAh
ITPodlpaOfZmIK
wvIrlwPMlLRRZO
SKJegFweBgEoxx
xbQkzuCvzVtXxP
ihuNUsTUgabUgb
rlWMtZufeJaDxf
cEgtFSRwJBRHom
ofUiKzoMgQDuVj
uYPLAHvbKrfTut
aGIlrXqEhcjfcD
esZvgBMAKcFSAo
XZROeCLbtGOIWy
GCIVkMkrGlfuLj
sHpfcJPvfIGaQr
TNdtOSMgKqukjK
mkedTWuzUAObrO
wAUizkpAXVnFgL
FpjNUVdRMlrfVk
WSlVzpkreOCrpj
gvtgKHxoffnfFX
uncmIhAdNWtDyK
sdkHIgFKCTxhDn
sdzwxzOfxiSuNI
iftbrdVteFLONl
eEnpsZYfXUHNss
ykhcRywnGsXMqD
uiMUCOfSlFZNBT
VptOIkNhHGtiGt
qzvrAmVzLcFibK
FEdJQBrGdQWcWj
KvegFCnLJLmNEq
WcYwYnndWIjTwb
aNVViVRULmNShf
QPKqWlGSSoLFrA
gDNpSwwHXbwmqb
kZPOQyzXjkdVmp
NRNSzMmMHNpBMr
pqyZtZPMZptmbZ
Yoroi Akado
Uchiha Sasuke
To think it'd be so soon...?!
I couldn't ask for more.
No way...!
Why Sasuke-kun?!
Now then, the two displayed on
the signboard, come forward.
For the 1st battle, Akado Yoroi and
Uchiha Sasuke have been selected.
No objections, right?
— Right.
— No!
All I can do now is watch...
Sasuke-kun...
Sasuke!
If you want to fight me, don't lose!
Sasuke-kun... You're acting strange...
Is it because of the Curse Mark...?
Sasuke-kun, do your best!
I guess I'll wait and see...
The pain won't go away!
It appears the Curse Mark hurts.
Now then, we will begin the first battle.
Everyone other than the two foes,
please move to the upper area.
Hey! Kakashi-sensei!
Sasuke!
Huh?
Don't use the Sharingan.
So you knew?
If that Curse Mark on your neck
gets out of control,
it could endanger your life.
I believe it.
Well, the match will be
called off at that time.
I'll be coming in to stop it,
so good luck.
Called off, you say?!
It seems this Curse Mark thing
is responding to my Chakra.
This is my final Chakra...
Sharingan!
Sasuke-kun, stop using the Sharingan!
If I carelessly build up Chakra,
it would extract my spirit energy,
and bring out the Chakra
inside my body to no end.
In other words, in this match,
I can hardly use even my regular Jutsu,
not to mention the Sharingan!
However... Yoroi's ability is
the worst for you, Sasuke-kun.
Now then... How will I go...?
Don't act rashly... Sasuke.
Now then, please begin.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Oh no!
He did it!
My strength...?!
W-What is this?
My body strength has suddenly...!
Sasuke-kun!
Sasuke...!
You... my Chakra...
You just noticed now...?
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
Damn it!
The pain won't go away!
This damned Curse Mark is
responding all the time!
But I won't let this
exam get called off!
How will I do?
How should I fight?
Am I strong?
All I want is the answer to that.
I won't let this thing swallow me up
in a place like this!
Next episode:
"Super Eyebrows Jealous! "Lion Combo" is Born!"